[{"answer": "Listen, I'm no fan of this president and I'm certainly no fan of this president's foreign policy.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "You support, you're a Republican, I should reiterate here, you support the President's proposal to strike on Syria, what convinced you?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Congressman Grayson, you also have been part of this security briefings, have you not?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well clearly we don't have to strike, I think that's indubitable.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "You don't believe we have to strike, you don't feel the same moral compunction to act, why not?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "I think Alan's comments point out that there are a lot of questions here and frankly the President has a lot of work to do to convince the American people that this is the appropriate course of action.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "What are you hearing from your constituents?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well he's going to have to, listen again, I am no fan of this President, I'm no fan of this President's foreign policy.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "And you think the President, can he make that case Tuesday night when he speaks to the nation in what will be a major address?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "The public has the right to decide when this country goes to war.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "The public's not always right are they?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Well suppose to act as representatives and that's why you're seeing such a divergence with the House.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "I mean Congress, Congress like this I thought you said has the right to decide when the country goes to war?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Please.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Can I finish?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I've seen everything that she's seen and there's nothing else there.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "The death of 1400 people including 400 children which the President seems to be emphasizing right now in Syria, if that's true that doesn't convince you that the United States should get involved?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Actually I would reclassify what you said Piers (ph) good evening, a sad evening.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Am I correct sir?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well I mean, the facts that I see is report from BBC by Carla Del Ponte from a few month ago when the initial chemical attack occurred April or March and her words were very clear.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "The British now say they've actually tested and found Sarin and gas itself there, you don't believe that to be the case?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "First of all I am pro strike against Assad regime.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Let me first of all ask you to respond to the doctor we just heard there, who suggested right now, there's a difference between opposition and terrorism, what do you say to that?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Thank you so much for raising such an important question and I think the New York Times owe us an apology.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "How do you convince the American people that an air strike isn't helping the individuals behind brutality like that?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "No they are not apt to begin with, I mean let's just remember our history.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Are these apt comparisons, do you think?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Oh I agree with Fareed with every word said completely in, I don't think even Rwanda's an analogy of what's going on right now.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Is Rwanda a better historical comparison?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "No, I mean obviously if it's nuclear weapons that you would have NATO involved here.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Would there be this debate right now about whether the US should act?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "AKARIA: Absolutely, Doug is absolutely right.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Would he have been better off if he had bombed right away?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well it's -- it will probably be the President's fault if that's the way you want to look at it but I also am not on so doomsday that this is the end of the Obama Administration.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "The bombing never happens and say things get worse in Syria, will this be the President's fault or will this be Congress' fault?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, it's always hard -- people forget it's very hard to get a Democratic Republic to get onboard with any war.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Why isn't he made more progress convincing the American people?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, the whole thing it makes you -- you're giving your enemy at least 10 days warning, they've got time to move things around, hide things and alter the entire landscape of where you'd have to attack.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "This makes you crazy as a military guy this delay?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I don't understand why...", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "ORDAN: So, did General Dempsey enable this on the one end by saying like, \"Oh\", you know, giving the OK?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "I think he's in absolutely a worst position.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "As the President arrives home from this trip, did he arrive home in a better position than when he left on the issue of Syria?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "I mean did you support the Iraq war?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Yes, taking him out.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Take him out?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "It made me feel afraid.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "How did that that make you guys feel?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Have you ever experienced any kind of racism in this town?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I ran into him last year.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Have either you bumped into this man yet?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I think it's unclear.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "What are the plans that this community has right now to deal with Paul Craig Cobb?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130906pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Is everyone who lives there, where they rallied around you against this guy?", "qSentId": 432}]